RG 079:005, Department of Environmental Protection: Air, Waste and Water
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Bureau of Water Management, 1920-1979
  - Ansonia Water Company, 1920; 1999-016
    - "Report and Valuation Property and Plant of the Ansonia Water Company, Volume II, Inventory", 1920 (Box 1)
- Series 15. Bureau of Air Management, 1975-1992
  - Director's Subject Files, 1975-1987; 1998-037
    - Air Administration (Box 1)
    - American Cyanamid re: Sampling (Box 1)
    - Carbon Monoxide (Box 1)
    - E.P.A. (Box 1)
    - Environmental Quality - Air - Administration (Box 1)
    - Laboratories layout (Box 1)
    - Lead Special Equivalency, Hartford N.U. Specials (Box 1)
    - Lead standard (Box 1)
    - National Commission on Air Quality Studies (Box 1)
    - NSPS (New Source Performance Standards) (Box 1)
    - SIPS (State Implementatin Plan) (Box 1)
    - Toxic Air Pollutants - 2 (Box 1)
    - Toxic Air Pollutants - 3 (Box 1)
    - Wood Burning (Box 1)
  - Hearings, 1988-1992; 1993-145
    - Bio-Gen Wood Buring Facility, Torrington, Hearing, 1990 October - 1991 August
      - Briegs of concerned citizens, hearing summary and newspaper clippings (Box 1)
      - Exhibits and miscellaneous drawings (Box 2)
      - DEP correspondence and documents (Box 3)
      - Documents and general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Exhibits (Box 5)
      - Transcripts (Box 6)
        - 1990 December 5, 6, 7, 12, 14, 18, 19 (Box 6)
        - 1991 January 3, 19, 11, 14, 15, 18, 23, 25 (Box 6)
        - 1991 July 31 (Box 6)
        - 1990 October 18, 26, 28, 30 (Box 7)
        - 1990 November 7, 9, 13, 14, 16, 19, 30 (Box 7)
        - 1991 August 6 (Box 7)
        - 1991 August 9 (Box 7)
    - CRRA Mid Connecticut Resource Reecovery Facility, Hartford, Hearing, 1994 January - 1985
      - Exhibits (Box 8-9)
        Contents are internal documents and correspondence.
      - Transscripts (Box 10)
        - 1984 October 17-19 (Box 10)
        - 1985 January 24 (Box 10)
      - Continued hearing transcripts
        - 1984 October 25, 26, 30 (Box 10)
        - 1984 November 1 (Box 10)
        - 1984 November 2 (Box 10)
    - Sterling Tire Burning Plant, Sterling, Hearing, 1988 August - October
      - Exhibits (Box 11)
        Consists of internal documents, modeling results and general correspondence.
    - Killingly Wood Burning Facility, Killingly, Hearing, 1992 January - May
      - Internal documents and corresopndence (Box 12)
      - APP Series miscellaneous exhibits (Box 12)
      - DEP Series exhibits (Box 13)
        Consists of internal documents and correspondence.
      - ALA Series exhibits (Box 13)
        Consists of American Lung Association corresopndence and documents on Wood Buring Emiissions.
      - N Series exhibits (Box 13)
        Consists of National corresopndence and documentation of effects of wood buring from the Nation.
      - HO Series exhibits (Box 13)
        Conisists of letters fromt he public stating why a wood burning plant should not be built.
      - Siting Council exhibits (Box 14)
      - APP Series exhibits (Box 14)
        Consists of documents and corresopndence from applicant applying for the permit.
      - Briefs on notice issues from the hearing officer (Box 14)
      - Town exhibits (Box 15)
        Consists of correspondence and documents from the town of Killingly.
      - Handwritten notes from the hearing officer (Box 15)
      - Exhibits of compilation documents, 1988 October, 1991 November; 3-ring binders (Box 16)
      - Exhibits of compilation documents, 1988 April, 1990 September; 3-ring binders (Box 17)
      - Transcripts
        - 1992 January 9, 14, 16 (Box 18)
        - 1992 March 2, 4, 6, 9, 10, 16, 18, 19, 31 (Box 18)
        - 1992 January 29, 30 (Box 19)
        - 1992 February 3, 4, 18 (Box 19)
        - 1992 May 1, 4, 5, 13, 22, 27 (Box 19)
        - 1992 February 19, 21 (Box 20)
        - 1992 March 1, 2, 4, 6 (Box 20)
        - 1992 April 1, 15, 16, 20, 22, 27 (Box 20)
      - Copies of transcripts
        - 1992 March 9, 16, 18, 19, 31 (Box 21)
        - 1992 May 1, 4, 5, 13, 22, 27 (Box 21)
        - 1992 February 3, 4, 18, 19, 21 (Box 22)
        - 1992 January 6, 9, 14 (Box 22)
        - 1992 January 29, 30 (Box 23)
      - Echibits of compilation documents, 1998 September; 3-ring binder (Box 23)
      - Three 12 x 16 picture drawings (Box 21)
- Series 25. Inland Water Resources, 1939-2013
  - 1998-038, 2 cubic feet
    - Commissions and Committee Records
      - New England River Basins Commission, 1966-1975
        - Minutes of meeting, 1969 (Box 1)
        - Organization meeting, 1967 October 16 (Box 1)
        - State contribution - budget, etc. (Box 1)
        - Before 1967 (Box 1)
        - Study of small private dams (Box 1)
        - [untitled folder] (Box 1)
        - Wise use of flood plains (Box 1)
        - Water quality planning (Box 1)
        - Priority planning, 1971-1975 (Box 1)
        - Project priority data (Box 1)
        - Dworsky's "New England River Basins Commission" (Box 1)
        - Meeting, 1969 May 1 (Box 1)
        - Southeastern New England comprehensive study (Box 1)
        - Meeting, Providence, R.I., 1968 October 22-23 (Box 1)
        - North Atlantic Regional Water Resources Study (Box 1)
          - Agendas (Box 1)
          - Appendices (Box 1)
          - Reports by states (Box 1)
      - Connecticut Soil Conservation Advisroy Committee, 1948-1974
        - Minutes, 1948 (Box 2)
        - Minutes, 1949 (Box 2)
        - Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
        - Minutes, payment vouchers, schedule of meetings, committee members, bylaws, 1968 (Box 2)
        - Minutes, payment vouchers, schedule of meetings, committee members, bylaws, 1969 (Box 2)
        - Minutes, payment vouchers, schedule of meetings, committee members, bylaws, 1970 (Box 2)
        - Windham County Soil Conservation District Board of Supervisors, 1958-1961 (Box 2)
        - Middlesex County Soil & Water Conservation District Supervisors, 1969-1974 (Box 2)
      - Survey notes of Connecticut waterways, 1939-1941; 8 notebooks + 1 index (Box 2)
  - 2014-036, .25 cubic feet
    - Municipal Inland Wetland Commissioners Training Program, 2007-2013
      - Introduction: Connecticut's Inland Wetlands and Watercourses Act volume 1a, 2007; 1 DVD, 1 hour, 30 min., 36 sec. (Box 1)
      - An Introduction to Map Reading & Site Plan Review volume 2, 2010; 1 DVD, 1 hour, 6 min., 5 sec. (Box 1)
      - The Functions and Values of Wetlands and Watercourses volume 3, 2013; 1 DVD, 41 min., 37 sec. (Box 1)